<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<document>
   <title>
      <translation lang="en">User Manual</translation>
   </title>
   <meta>
      <owner>tamirhassan</owner>
      <date-of-creation>Thu Feb 07 2019 12:11:12 </date-of-creation>
      <date-of-last-change>Thu Feb 07 2019 12:16:46 </date-of-last-change>
      <language>en-GB</language>
      <status>1</status>
      <description>Short Description</description>
      <logo-image>././client/data/6e6e6aca-a277-4723-b232-354c9dc2d0df/logo.png</logo-image>
      <cover-image>././client/data/6e6e6aca-a277-4723-b232-354c9dc2d0df/cover.png</cover-image>
      <main-title>New Map</main-title>
      <subtitle>New Subtitle</subtitle>
      <cover-text>n/a</cover-text>
      <structure>
         <format>info</format>
         <chapter-on-right-page/>
         <cover-backpage/>
      </structure>
      <design>
         <layout>columns</layout>
         <paper-format>A4</paper-format>
         <page-margin>leftright</page-margin>
         <spaces>large</spaces>
         <header>longheader</header>
         <footer>shortfooter</footer>
         <look-and-feel>fashion</look-and-feel>
         <table-layout>simple</table-layout>
      </design>
   </meta>
   <toc/>
   <chapter hyphenation="yes" chapterpage="no" id="615a8921-7d8a-4859-b4bd-58250d42c622"
            ismodule="no">
      
         <title>
            <title id="b4b08f9e-d370-4392-8e5d-8d70e257cb57">ICDAR 2013 Table Competition</title>
         </title>
         
            <column-wide-element>
         <p>Abstract—Table understanding is a well studied problem in
document analysis, and many academic and commercial approaches have been developed to recognize tables in several
document formats, including plain text, scanned page images
and born-digital, object-based formats such as PDF. Despite the
abundance of these techniques, an objective comparison of their
performance is still missing. The Table Competition held in
the context of ICDAR 2013 is our first attempt at objectively
evaluating these techniques against each other in a standardized
way, across several input formats. The competition independently
addresses three problems: (i) table location, (ii) table structure
recognition, and (iii) these two tasks combined. We received
results from seven academic systems, which we have also compared against four commercial products. This paper presents our
findings</p>
      </column-wide-element>
            <column-wide-element>
         <p>The problem of analysing tables in documents has been
dealt with in many academic publications over the previous
two decades. The systems reported in the literature vary
according to the input document format (ASCII text, HTML,
image, PDF) and the type of structure that is recognized and
output by the system.
Table understanding has been gaining traction since the
beginning of the big data era due to the massive amounts
of tabular data in documents on the Web. In addition, private,
public and governmental institutions often publish reports in
PDF format. Such data is immensely valuable for decision support and object search, but without reliable table understanding
techniques, it cannot be easily indexed by search engines or
used by automatic data processing applications.
In our previous work [1], we proposed a methodology for
evaluating these approaches independently from the format of
the input and of the output. In particular, the problem of table
understanding was split up into three tasks:</p>
      </column-wide-element>
         
      
   </chapter>
   <figure-index/>
   <footnote-index/>
   <index/>
</document>